$nade_ModName	Naked Defeat

$nade_OptionsLocalSlave	Local Slavery :Options:

$nade_NakedTravelCost	Save Travel Ritual Cost

$nade_AcheronBleedoutFix	Disable Acheron Handling
$nade_AcheronBleedoutFixHL	[x] disables all scripts in Naked Defeat that are listening for or handling the Acheron mod.

$nade_LootWeaponChance	Loot Weapon Chance
$nade_LootWeaponChanceHL	Sets the chance of a weapon beeing suitable for you to sue. At 50% a weapon will be either destroyed when equipped OR transformed into a suitable weapon of similar type from your saved weapon profiles. 

$nade_MouthOpenMax	Mouth Opening (Max)
$nade_MouthOpenMaxHL	This value allows you to set the Maximum Mouth opening of your Character during the Defeat Scenario. Note that this might also affect gags. I m working on more elaborate options for this.

$nade_ImmersiveRobbery	Immersive Robbery
$nade_ImmersiveRobberyHL	[ ] disabling this will prevent Robbery (from a Bandit somewhere in a random Bandit Cave) from happening when it would make sense immersionwise (on Slavery, Death, etc.) 

$nade_RobQuetItmes	Rob Quest Items
$nade_RobQuetItmesHL	[x] allows robbing quest items [ ] prevents robbing quest items

$nade_NymDarkWorld	Nymra's Dark World
$nade_NymDarkWorldHL	See PDF guide for details.

$nade_SS_SessionSlaveryWeight	Session Slave Weight
$nade_SS_SessionSlaveryWeightHL	Classic Sex Session Scenario we already know. You are sold to a random Location, bound and fucked and then left to wiggle your way to freedom.

$nade_OnlyBreathing	Hard Labor Breathing Weight 
$nade_OnlyBreathingHL	Sets the chance to hear Breathing sounds instead of SexLab Moans during Hard Slave Labor. Setting this to 100% means you will only get Breathing sounds. 0% results in 90% SexlabMoans.

$nade_LootWeapons	Loot Weapons
$nade_LootWeaponsHL	[x] with this enabled Weapons are also processed and switched with saved Weapons from your Profiles. [ ] If you disable this, Weapons will not be effected at all by Naked Loot. 

$nade_StripWeaponOptions	Weapon Handling
$nade_StripWeaponOptionsHL	Allows seperate Strip Options for Weapons (and Shields). Exluded means that Naked Loot will ignore Weapons. They will not be unequipped or destroyed or dropped by the mod.
$nade_StripWeaponOptionsListUnequip	Unequipped
$nade_StripWeaponOptionsListDrop	Dropped
$nade_StripWeaponOptionsListDestroy	Destroyed
$nade_StripWeaponOptionsListExclude	Excluded

$nade_SS_LocalSlaveryWeight	Local Slave Weight

$nade_NymCombat	Nymra's Combat Features
$nade_NymCombatHL	[x] Uses Ragdoll! Enables Surprise Attacks (you are hit outside combat) and Push Attacks from Power Attacks/Big Creatures. Immersive Combat features for certain Creatures based on their type and size. Detailed Walkthrough in the PDF.

$nade_LocalSlavery	Enable Local Slavery
$nade_RequestKey	Slave Action Key
$nade_SubmitKey	Submit Key
$nade_TaskValue	Task Value

$nade_BodyFluids	Dripping Pussy
$nade_BodyFluidsHL	[x] with this enabled Naked Defeat will equip a dripping pussy effect on certain occasions. Does NOT affect Pee, Wetness or similar things.

$nade_PriceOfFreedomMin	Price of Freedom (min)
$nade_PriceOfFreedomMax	Price of Freedom (max)

$nade_AllowCityEscape	Allow Escape from Public Slavery
$nade_AllowCityEscapeHL	[x] with this enabled you can leave the vicinity of the Slavery Location BEFORE paying all the Gold for your Freedom (your Bounty will go up tho). If not, you will always magically be teleport back and punished for the attemp.

$nade_BodyShaders	Body Shaders
$nade_BodyShadersHL	[ ] Disables ALL Punishment Shaders (Shock, Frost, Fire etc.) - more elaborate options are planned - WARNING! This can lead to strange situations and some screen messages or scenes might not match. I do NOT recommend using this. Only if you are annoyed by the shaders and know what you disable, feel free.

$nade_NakedRunning	Naked Running
$nade_NakedRunningHL	[x] lets Naked Defeat handle your Speed completely (Speedmult). See PDF for full documentation.

$nade_NakedRunningSpeed	Base Speed
$nade_NakedRunningSpeed	HL	Sets the base speed to work with. I recommend not using anything too far from 100 (90-130) or you will get slow or immobile or very fast. High and low values are in the slider for playtesting too.

$nade_NakedTripping	Naked Tripping
$nade_NakedTrippingHL	[x] adds a chance to stumble and fall over when barefoot. See PDF for full documentation. 

$nade_DefeatSpeedMult	Cage Slave Weight
$nade_DefeatSpeedMultHL	Set the chance of Simple Slavery sending you to the new Naked Defeat Cage Escape game. You are trapped in a cage and have to fuck your way out. Scenario will be greatly expanded in the future.

$nade_ImmersionRobbery	Immersive Robbery
$nade_ImmersionRobberyHL	[x] With this Option ON you will be robbed before dieing (Afterlife) or before beeing sold as a Slave. This is not tied to the Robbery Chance (but respects Rob Gold Only). If this is enabled you will ALWAYS be robbed before Death/Slavery.

$nade_DefeatDDChance	(2nd Roll) Devious Devices Chance
$nade_DefeatDDChanceHL	Requires DDNG to work - 2nd Roll (after Scenario Chance) to determine if you are bound with Devious Devices before the rape.

$nade_DeviousPiercingEffects	Devious Piercing Effects
$nade_DeviousPiercingEffectsHL	[x] with this enabled you can not equip Body armor while wearing DD piercings. You can also only wiggle free of them when you are close to a workbench (100 units, you dont need to use it) or if you have Piercing Tools.

$nade_NakedCumming	Naked Cumming [Orgasm Control]
$nade_NakedCummingHL	[x] with this enabled Naked Defeat will take control of Orgasms from Sexlab. All Actors will orgasm kind of random, with a higher chance towards the end of the scene. All can be multiorgasmic, females more than males. Stages can be repeated to satisfy actors. Might be incompatible with SLSO and similar mods.

$nade_SSHandling	Simple Slavery Additions
$nade_SSHandlingHL	[x] with this enabled you get: Sounds and Expressions during Auction. Your Followers get sold with you next to the platform. I m also working on a Travel Fun Scenario, a Slave Rape and other stuff. Stay tuned.  

$nade_HeelsFix	Fix High Heels Height (BETA)
$nade_HeelsFixHL	[x] with this enabled Naked Defeat will try to adjust your characters height when wearing high heels during the Defeat Scenario. Compatible with Sexlabs "Adjust High Heels Hight" (I suggest having that enabled too). 

$nade_KeyDDWiggleFreeFailChance	Wiggle Free Critical Failure Chance
$nade_KeyDDWiggleFreeFailChanceHL	Requires DD NG. At 0% you well never be punished for trying to wiggle free. At 100% you will ALWAYS get punished when you fail to wiggle free (Wiggle Free Chance). Recommend to set this between 5% and 20%. Punishments currently: sold as slave or Afterlife. More will come.  

$nade_KeyDDWiggleFreeChance	Wiggle Free Chance with Action Key
$nade_KeyDDWiggleFreeChanceHL	Requires DD NG. Set to 0% to disable. If 1% or more, you have that chance to wiggle free from ALL Devious Devices during an animated Scene. Bad Outcomes can happen. Feature is WIP and will be more detailled in the future.

$nade_Options	System

$nade_SurrenderOptions	Surrender Options

$nade_NakedFalling	Naked Accidents
$nade_NakedFallingHL	(This was "Naked Falling" before) Set to 0 to disable. Set the Dice Size for Accidents to happen. If you set this slider to 100 and you receive 20 damage OUTSIDE of Combat, there is a 20% chance for an accident. Ambushes, Death/Afterlife, Rescue or waking up somewhere randomly.

$nade_ShowInfoMessages	Show Info Messages
$nade_ShowInfoMessagesHL	Displays in orange color informational messages about the mods inner workings (mostly chances and helpful information). Disable when you know your way around later on.

$nade_ShowNarrativeMessages	Show Narrative Messages
$nade_ShowInfoMessagesHL	Displays in red color the narrative messages that lead you through the scenario. I recommend keeping it on, but if you are annoyed by it feel free to disable them.

$nade_LagFix	LagFix (experimental)
$nade_LagFixHL	This is the attempt to reduce lag during the scenario by leaving "Activate" enabled. Should reduce script lag and increase response time. Report your findings please. DO NOT ACTIVATE STUFF DURING DEFEAT THO! :)

$nade_RemoveDDChance	Remove DD Chance [DD]
$nade_RemoveDDChanceHL	Sets the chance of your captors removing all devious devices from your character before the fucking. If DDs are not removed Naked Defeat will try to start a special scenario now.

$nade_DefeatFindSpot	Time to find a Spot for Sex
$nade_DefeatFindSpotHL	OFF: you will be fucked on the spot where you are Defeated - UNLIMITED: you have infinite time to find a suitable spot. Press ActionKey "K" when you found one - TIMER: you have only the set time in seconds. You can skip the remaining time with ActionKey "K")

$nade_DefeatEscapeCrawl	Time to Escape from Enemies
$nade_DefeatEscapeCrawlHL	OFF: you will be attacked immediately after escaping - UNLIMITED: you have infinite time to escape from your enemies. Press ActionKey "K" when you feel save (or want to attack them) - TIMER: you have only the set escape time in seconds. You can skip the remaining time with ActionKey "K")

$nade_NakedTravelling	Naked Travelling
$nade_NakedTravellingHL	[x] disables fast travel. You can enable fast travel for 1 Minute by performing in a Fast Travel Ritual (Action Wheel Shift+K). The "Risky" Ritual can lead to unwanted outcomes.

$nade_DefeatSpotAndEscape	Enable Find Spot & Escape
$nade_DefeatSpotAndEscapeHL	[x] You will have infinite time of finding a spot for the Defeat or to escape your Enemies. Press K when you found a spot or when you feel save.

$nade_NakedBlur	Disable Blur Effects
$nade_NakedBlurHL	[x] will disable the Blur Effects that I use to cover up ugly gaps between scenes (not recommended)

$nade_NakedChance	Defeat Chance (On Naked Hit)
$nade_NakedChanceHL	This setting only applies when you are hit on a slot with NO armor or clothing. Warning! Defeat Chance is much higher compared to On Strip so do NOT set this % too high when you want a "fair" naked fight. 

$nade_NoCrawling	Disable Crawl Animations
$nade_NoCrawlingHL	[x] disables the animation switch to crawl for the duration of the Defeat Scenario. This is meant for ppl who dont like those or have problems with them. From feedback the animations should work with only "FNIS", "FNIS & Nemesis" and "Nemesis only" approaches.

$nade_DefeatForeplayChance	ForePlay Chance
$nade_DefeatForeplayChanceHL	Sets the chance to see a ForePlay Scene before a normal SexScene at Round 1. Following Rounds have only low chance (Round 2 at 15% and 3 at 5%) and only if foreplay triggered on round 1. Only 2P scenes for now and only humans (working on group and creature tho).

$nade_PunishSexChance	Sex Weight (for Escape Game)
$nade_PunishSexChanceHL	Warning: do NOT set this too high or you will be fucked for days. Sets the chance of another round of Sex. The Furniture will be removed and you will be fucked again respecting the Group and ChainFuck Options.

$nade_PunishBukkakeChance	Bukkake Weight (for Escape Game)
$nade_PunishBukkakeChanceHL	Warning: do NOT set this too high or you will only see dicks for days. Sets the chance of captors coming up to you and masturbate while you are forced to watch and... well... receive.

$nade_PunishWhipChance	Whipping Weight (for Escape Game)
$nade_PunishWhipChanceHL	This sets the chance to be punished with the whip while already struggling (Duration is Whip Time (General)). The general Whip chance below is a separate value that determines the primary whipping scene after Sex or when having a Short Scenario.

$nade_CooperativeSurrenderChance	Cooperative Surrender Chance
$nade_CooperativeSurrenderChanceHL	When surrendering this value is the chance of having a Short Defeat Scenario (only 1 scene), no matter what you set for that to happen. This means if you surrender in time instead of beeing forced down your enemies will be less brutal and steal less of your time :)

$nade_SkipSex	Skip Sex Content
$nade_SkipSexHL	[x] skips ALL Sex Scenes from Naked Defeat except GoldenShowers (you can set that to 0% already).


$nade_NymBeta	Nymra's BETA Features
$nade_NymBetaHL	[x] enables Features that are in development. Check the changelogs or ask me in the support forum for the features in question, I am always looking for BETA testers

$nade_StageGoBack	Insatiable Sex Partners
$nade_StageGoBackHL	[x] SexScenes will randomly go back a stage.

$nade_FindSpotTime	Find Spot TIMER
$nade_FindSpotTimeHL	With this you can control how long you have to find a good spot before Defeat starts. Requires to set Time to find Spot for Sex to "TIMER"

$nade_WeaponOutSurrender	Surrender only with weapon out
$nade_WeaponOutSurrenderHL	with this toggled ON you can only surrender when you have your weapon drawn in combat. This is for ppl who suffer from the bad combat detection of skyrim.

$nade_DefeatArrestProb	Arrest chance
$nade_DefeatArrestProbHL	Chance of beeing arrested via Prison Overhaul Patched after Public Punishment ends. Only occurs when there is no short punishment and currently arrests for 1500 crimegold.

$nade_DefeatShortProb	Short Defeat Chance
$nade_DefeatShortProbHL	Chance that defeat will only be one scene instead of the full defeat cycle. Can be either one of the following: "Fucking", "Golden Shower", "Whipping", "Wiggle Free", Whipping or Golden Showers on 0% will not use those scenes.

$nade_NoExtra	Disable hidden variables
$nade_NoExtraHL	[x] disables the hidden proximity variables of public punishment. proximity can trigger even when you follow ALL the rules but get too close to civilians or especially guards.

$nade_PoisonDefeat	Poisoned Potions
$nade_PoisonDefeatChance	Defeat Chance (from potions)
$nade_PoisonDefeatChanceHL	Sets the chance of beeing poisoned from consuming potions during combat (perverted alchemists...). This Feature is WIP and will be expanded with options to include noncombat scenarios and also food, ingredients etc.


$DescriptionSaveOutfits Your saved outfits. They will survive updates but not a reinstall or a new game. It is recommended to not have more than two outfits of one type (only 2 heavy armor etc.) because the random engine will never pick the third if it exists... :(

$nade_StripOptions	Stripped item is:
$nade_StripOptionsHL	Choose how stripped items are handled. Unequiped (still in inventory), dropped to the ground (can be picked back up) or destroyed (lost forever!)
$nade_StripOptionsListUnequip	Unequipped
$nade_StripOptionsListDrop	Dropped
$nade_StripOptionsListDestroy	Destroyed

$nade_StripOptions	Stripped item is:
$nade_StripOptionsHL	Choose how stripped items are handled. Unequiped (still in inventory), dropped to the ground (can be picked back up) or destroyed (lost forever!)
$nade_StripOptionsListUnequip	Unequipped
$nade_StripOptionsListDrop	Dropped
$nade_StripOptionsListDestroy	Destroyed

$nade_WiggleOptions	Escape Difficulty (Defeat)
$nade_WiggleOptionsHL	Set the difficulty for the escape chance from Devices (Capture Event). Hard (1%), Medium (3%), Easy (5%), Easiest (10%), Random Hard tends to have 50% of times 1% chances etc. 
$nade_WiggleOptionsListHard	Hard
$nade_WiggleOptionsListMedium	Medium
$nade_WiggleOptionsListEasy	Easy
$nade_WiggleOptionsListEasiest	Easiest
$nade_WiggleOptionsListRandom_Hard	Random Hard
$nade_WiggleOptionsListRandom_Medium	Random Medium
$nade_WiggleOptionsListRandom_Easy	Random Easy
$nade_WiggleOptionsListRandom_Easiest	Random Easiest

$nade_WiggleOptionsSS	Escape Difficulty (Slavery)
$nade_WiggleOptionsSSHL	Set the difficulty for the escape chance from Devices (after Sold as Slave event). Hard (1%), Medium (3%), Easy (5%), Easiest (10%), Random Hard tends to have 50% of times 1% chances etc. 
$nade_WiggleOptionsSSListHard	Hard
$nade_WiggleOptionsSSListMedium	Medium
$nade_WiggleOptionsSSListEasy	Easy
$nade_WiggleOptionsSSListEasiest	Easiest
$nade_WiggleOptionsSSListRandom_Hard	Random Hard
$nade_WiggleOptionsSSListRandom_Medium	Random Medium
$nade_WiggleOptionsSSListRandom_Easy	Random Easy
$nade_WiggleOptionsSSListRandom_Easiest	Random Easiest

$nade_DefeatFindSpotList_OFF	OFF
$nade_DefeatFindSpotList_UNLIMITED	UNLIMITED
$nade_DefeatFindSpotList_TIMER	TIMER

$nade_DefeatEscapeCrawlList_OFF	OFF
$nade_DefeatEscapeCrawlList_UNLIMITED	UNLIMITED
$nade_DefeatEscapeCrawlList_TIMER	TIMER

$nade_NymStripping	Nymra's Strip Service
$nade_NymStrippingHL	[x] Strips body armor on bleedout. Strips arm and leg armor before Captivity. 33% Chance to strip almost completly naked before first Sex Scene. Can possibly break DD items

$nade_VRfix	SexlabP+ & VR fix
$nade_VRfixHL	[x] should fix issues with actor placement in SexlabP+ and issue of the VR camera spinning during the defeat scenario. This disables the vehicle, so player can be pushed around by NPC or whip hits and end up in weird spots

$nade_SSEfix	SSE chain hdt fix
$nade_SSEfixHL	[x] Prevents HDT items from beeing equiped. Check this if the hdt chains added during the cuffs/yoke escape scenario look bad, crash your game etc. the fix currently just prevents the chain from beeing equiped

$nade_Defeat	Defeat & Sex
$nade_Debug	Debug
$nade_DebugPunishmentType	Punishment Debug (dont use)
$nade_DebugPunishmentTypeHL	Only for testing and works only with "Show Debug Messages" enabled (in System). Usage: set the punishment type you want to "test" according to your list above --- IMPORTANT --- you cannot wiggle free with this on, you can only break free via debug hotkey!

nade_DefeatStartOptions	Start Options

$nade_BleedoutCounter	Defeat Chance (On Bleedout)
$nade_BleedoutCounterHL	Sets the %Chance of Defeat starting on Bleedout. Set this to 100% to always start Defeat when you reach Bleedout (0 HP).

$nade_CriticalDefeat	Defeat Chance (On Strip)
$nade_CriticalDefeatHL	Critical Defeat: Only works when Combat Strip is ON: Activate this to have a chance to start Defeat Scenario when an item is stripped on hit (Recommended when your Character is very powerfull and bleedout happens rarely) - Important: do not set this too low or it might trigger almost never (frist strip chance, then critical defeat chance...)

$nade_DefeatWhipTime	Whipping Time
$nade_DefeatWhipTimeHL	Sets the time that whipping scenes will last. The slider only applies for whipping outside of sex scenes (for whipping in furniture etc.)

$nade_StripAttack	Ripping Attacks
$nade_StripAttackHL	[x] Attacks from dogs, wolves, skeevers, spriggans and trolls and also power attacks from all sources have a higher chance to strip armor in combat and TWICE the chance for a critical defeat on strip (so if you set Critical Defeat chance to 5%, a Ripping Attack has 10% chance of starting the Defeat)

$nade_ExposureChance	General Exposure Chance
$nade_ExposureChanceHL	All weights are rolled against this value. Example: If you set Nakedness Weight to 50 and General Exposure chance to 100 you have a 50% chance to get +1 Exposure per Scan Tick.

$nade_LoopTime	Scan Frequency
$nade_LoopTimeHL	Determines how often the scan runs in cities. If you have lag when setting this low, try a longer time. Every time the scan happens, exposure is determined by rolling weight vs exposure chance.

$nade_Naked_Weight	Nakedness Weight
$nade_Naked_WeightHL	Sets the chance to get exposure for beeing naked

$nade_Barefoot_Weight	Barefoot Weight
$nade_Barefoot_WeightHL	Sets the chance to get exposure for beeing barefoot (only if you are NOT naked)

$nade_DefeatRescueProb	Rescue Chance
$nade_DefeatRescueProbHL	Sets the chance for beeing rescued and brought to an nearby city or inn. If no nearest hold can be found, a random hold is selected.

$nade_FemalesAsMales	Females in Male position
$nade_FemalesAsMalesHL	Chance to see females in male positions in a sex scene. Recommended to use with Futa (adds schlong to females) or StrapOns (configurable in Sexlab MCM). Otherwise the SexSceneFilter will always try to put females in female scenes (if your PC is female and the aggressor is female it will play FF animations only)

$nade_Dirty_Weight	Dirtyness Weight
$nade_Dirty_WeightHL	Sets the chance to get exposure for beeing dirty (requires the mod: Bathing in Skyrim or this will do nothing)

$nade_Sneaking_Weight	Sneak Weight
$nade_Sneaking_WeightHL	Sets the chance to get exposure for sneaking. It is planned to consider sneaking skill as reduction for this in the future.

$nade_Running_Weight	Running Weight
$nade_Running_WeightHL	Sets the chance to get exposure for running

$nade_Sprinting_Weight	Sprinting Weight
$nade_Sprinting_WeightHL	Sets the chance to get exposure for sprinting

$nade_Cum_Weight	Cumsoaked Weight
$nade_Cum_WeightHL	Sets the chance to get exposure for beeing covered in cum (from Sexlab)

$nade_Unarmed_Weight	Unarmed Weight
$nade_Unarmed_WeightHL	Sets the chance to get exposure for beeing unarmed


$nade_NoEssentialPlayer	Remove Player Essential Flag
$nade_NoEssentialPlayerHL	[x]: removes Naked Defeats Bleedout handling, deactivating the bleedout Defeat start completly. If you still want Naked Defeat to work, you have to manually surrender in fights or use Critical Defeat (MCM - Extras - Combat Stripping) to start the Defeat Scenario.

$nade_GodMode	GodMode during Defeat
$nade_GodModeHL	[x] adds 100.000 HP to prevent unwanted deaths during Sex/Whipping from unwanted sources. HP is reset after Defeat Ends. 


$nade_HealthBoost	HealthBoost during Defeat
$nade_HealthBoostHL	[x] adds 100.000 HP to prevent unwanted deaths during Sex/Whipping from unwanted sources. HP is reset after Defeat Ends.

$nade_MoanOnHitChance	Moan on Hit Chance
$nade_MoanOnHitChanceHL	[x]: will play a Sexlab Medium sound (moan) whenever you are hit in combat or with a whip also from other mods. Might be incompatible/doubling with mods like PC head Tracking. Set to 0% to disable.

$nade_BleedoutChance	Option 2: Random Chance
$nade_BleedoutCounterHL	/!\ Needs option 1 to be set to 0X /!\ Whenever you enter bleedout this sets the chance to start the Defeat Scenario. If the chance is not met you will get up with full hp for another round of combat.

$nade_RemoveDDs	Remove DD items
$nade_RemoveDDsHL	[Requires mod: DDequip] This will attempt to remove some (not all) DDs at the beginning of the Defeat Scenario. Highly recommended or the mods idles and animations will look broken. If you want to be be bound again after the mod is over, choose Captivity event 100% and Captivity DDe chance 100%.

$nade_AllowCreatures	Allow Animals & Humanoid Creatures
$nade_AllowCreaturesHL	[ ]: If this is NOT checked all humanoid creatures and all animals will be ignored (including Draugrs, Falmers etc) and if there are no humans around to fuck the player, the player will get up from bleedout with full health. If you want a more detailled approach use Creature Toggles in MCM with this Option enabled [x]
$nade_FemalesAllowed	Allow Female enemies for Sex

$nade_SearchRadius	Scan Radius (Outdoors)
$nade_SearchRadiusHL	This allows to customize the range of the Scan Outdoors (in the streets, wilderness, etc.) for possible sex partners in the area. 1000 is ~14 metres, 10000 ~140 metres. TIPP: set this low outdoors to prevent uninvoled actors from joining in.

$nade_SearchRadiusInterior	Scan Radius (Indoors)
$nade_SearchRadiusInteriorHL	This allows to customize the range of the Scan Indoors (houses, dungeons, etc.) for possible sex partners in the area. 1000 is ~14 metres, 10000 ~140 metres. TIPP: Should be save to set to high radius because indoors its more likely to have suitable actors even further away.

$nade_DefeatPeeProb	Golden Shower Chance
$nade_DefeatPeeProbHL	[Requires - Extras - "Forced Bathing"] The chance for triggering a golden shower event before Sex. If Bathing in Skyrim is installed (latest version from monoman1) will wash the PC clean!

$nade_ToggleDeleteDevice	Clean up Furniture
$nade_ToggleDeleteDeviceHL	Deletes the furniture after the player escapes from it

$nade_PlayExpressions	Pain Expressions during Defeat
$nade_PlayExpressionsHL	Uncheck to disable Expressions played during the Defeat Scenario. Sexlab will still play Expressions during Sex of course. Also this setting does NOT overwrite Sexlab Expressions, those will play with this ON or OFF.

$nade_Group5Pchance	Chance for 5P scene
$nade_Group4Pchance	Chance for 4P scene
$nade_Group3Pchance	Chance for 3P scene
$nade_Group5PchanceHL	Chance for a 5P animation playing when there are 4 suitable attackers (human or creature). When set to 100% there will ALWAYS be 5P scene when enough attackers found. It is recommended to use a low % because there are only few 5P animations and so they should be played rarely. Up to you in the end...
$nade_Group4PchanceHL	Chance for a 4P animation playing when there are 3 or 4 suitable attackers (human or creature). When set to 100% there will ALWAYS be 4P scene when enough attackers found.
$nade_Group3PchanceHL	Chance for a 3P animation playing when there are 2, 3 or 4 suitable attackers (human or creature). When set to 100% there will ALWAYS be 3P scene when enough attackers found.

$nade_ScenarioChance	(1st Roll) Scenario Chance
$nade_ScenarioChanceHL	A random special scenario will be played (only for humans): Yoke, Cuffs, Armbinder, Pillory, XCross, Wheel, Rodeo, Girlfriend and many more. nadeConfig.json has additional options for these.

$nade_SexOptions	Sex Options

$nade_GangRape	GangFuck chance

$nade_ChainRape	ChainFuck chance
$nade_ChainRapeHL	Probability of being fucked more than once (three consecutive Sex scenes instead of one).

$nade_ActionKey	Action Key
$nade_ActionKeyHL	This key will work differently based on the circumstances (combat surrender, hair change, toggle public punishment etc.). See Mod Description on Loverslab (will the new list here later)

$nade_SimpleSurrender	Action Key leads to SimpleSlavery
$nade_SimpleSurrenderHL	[x]: Pressing the Action Hotkey while bound in furniture will send you to Simple Slavery. For use when you cannot get away from your enemies otherwise and do not want an easy escape still.

$nade_EscapeKey	Wiggle Key

$nade_HairOriginal	Original Hairstyle
$nade_HairCurrent	Current Hairstyle

$nade_EscapeDifficulty	Wiggle success chance
$nade_Robbery	Robbery chance

$nade_DefeatDDeProb	Devious Device weight [DD]
$nade_DefeatDDeProbHL	Requires: DD framework - Probability of getting locked in Devious Devices instead of furniture in captivity. With the slider on 0% you will always be bound to furnitures, with 100% always bound with DD items, with 50% equal chances for both happening. Both scenarios can have whipping.

$nade_Captivity	Captivity chance
$nade_ThrowOut	Outdoor Captivity chance
$nade_Slavery	Slavery chance

$nade_CaptivityOptions	Captivity Options

$nade_DefeatWhipProb	Whipping Chance (General)
$nade_DefeatWhipProbHL	Probability of a whipping event when captured (Captivity). Works both with furnitures and DDe outfit. Furnitures also have additional whipping punishment on failed escape attempts.

$nade_EscapeKeyHL	Hotkey to wiggle free from the furniture (press when you are bound to some contraption to try and break free)

$nade_NakedDrowning	Naked Swimming
$nade_NakedDrowningHL	With this enabled you will automatically strip heavy armor and boots during swimming.

$nade_Aftermath	Aftermath Options

$nade_DefeatSDweight	Slavery SD+ weight
$nade_DefeatSDweightHL	[Required: Sanguine Debauchery+] Allows to chose between Simple Slavery and Sanguine Debauchery+ on Slavery Event. If you set this to 100% you always get SD+, on 50% it will be equal chance.

$nade_EscTime	Escape TIMER
$nade_EscTimeHL	This sets the time in seconds it takes for your enemies to become hostile again at the end of the Defeat scenario. Requires to set Time to Escape from Enemies to "TIMER"

$nade_OtherOptions	Other Options

$nade_MaleFollower	Male Followers gets fucked
$nade_MaleFollowerHL	Allows your male follower to be fucked. If this is disabled, he will just be bound during Defeat.
$nade_FemaleFollower	Female Followers get fucked
$nade_FemaleFollowerHL	Allows your female follower to be fucked. If this is disabled, she will just be bound during Defeat.

$nade_RapeHandsProb	Dirty Hand Tattoo Chance



$nade_FemalesAllowedHL	Enables female enemies as dominant sex partners in sex scenes (if OFF you should never see female enemies in that role)

$nade_EscapeDifficultyHL	Set the difficulty for the escape chance from Devices (Capture Event). Hard (1%), Medium (3%), Easy (5%), Easiest (10%), Random Hard tends to have 50% of times 1% chances etc.
$nade_RobberyHL	Probability of assaulters stealing all equipment from the PC (works only with humans and humanoid creatures). You can try to get your stuff back, tho.

$nade_RobberyHL	Probability of assaulters stealing all equipment from the PC (works only with humans and humanoid creatures). You can try to get your stuff back, tho.






$nade_Traps	Trap Options
$nade_Ragdoll	Ragdoll
$nade_RagdollHL	[x]: will apply Ragdoll Effect on bleedout and when breaking free of furnitures. Increase Escape Alarm timer to at least 5 seconds or escape will become quite hard (takes longer to stand up) - use with my "ZAP Faster in and Out of Furnitures"!



$nade_Slippery	Slippery
$nade_SlipperyHL	[x]: chance of beeing stripped is DOUBLED when the character counts as cumsoaked.

$nade_DropItem	Drop items
$nade_DropItemHL	[x]: stripped items will be dropped on the ground instead of just getting unequipped. Happy searching...

$nade_Trap	Trap event chance

$nade_Threshold	Arousal threshold
$nade_Excite	Arousing traps

$nade_Stripping	Strip options

$nade_Nudity	Extras

$nade_Nudity	Extras
$nade_NuditySLA	Use SLA naked armor check
$nade_NudityUnderwear	Panty AND Bra slot items

$nade_Indecency	Public Punishment
$nade_IndecencyEnabled	Allow public punishment
$nade_Body	Library

$nade_BodyVisuals	Body Visuals & Tattoos

$nade_HairRegrowthTime	Hair regrowth time
$nade_WhipMarks	Whipmarks
$nade_RapeHands	Handprints




$nade_Clothing	Combat Stripping
$nade_BreakArmor	Enable Combat Strip & Critical Hits
$nade_BreakClothing	Clothing strip chance
$nade_BreakLight	Light armor strip chance
$nade_BreakHeavy	Heavy armor strip chance

$nade_ImprovisedItemsEnabled	Improvised Items
$nade_DisguiseEnabled	Disguise
$nade_SleepNaked	Sleep naked
$nade_SleepMast	Post-sleep masturbation

$nade_Poses	Poses

$nade_PosesSettings	Settings
$nade_PosesDefeat	Defeat poses
$nade_PosesShowPussy	Show off poses (pussy)
$nade_PosesShowAss	Show off poses (ass)
$nade_PosesPeeHi	Peeing poses (high)
$nade_PosesPeeLo	Peeing poses (low)
$nade_PosesDeflate	Deflation poses
$nade_PosesShower	Bathing poses (high)
$nade_PosesBath	Bathing poses (low)
$nade_PosesPiercing	Piercing poses
$nade_PosesShave	Haircut poses
$nade_PosesLoad	Load poses
$nade_PosesSelect	Select source
$nade_PosesSelect0	Cancel
$nade_PosesSelect1	Reset default poses
$nade_PosesSelect2	Import from PosesHotkey
$nade_PosesInterval	Interval (sec)

$nade_Debug	Debug

$nade_Settings	Settings

$nade_Enabled	Mod enabled
$nade_Messages	Show debug messages
$nade_MessagesHL	Enabled this shows internal messages needed for testing purposes. You can also see the Public Punish "Exposure" value to learn how it works and adjust it for your game. Careful! With this enabled you cannot break free from furniture without using the Action Key! 

$nade_FinishQuest	Finish quest

$nade_Variables1	Variables
$nade_Var10	Naked Defeat Mod Version
$nade_Var12	Slave status
$nade_Var13	Original hair
$nade_Var14	Current hair

$nade_Variables0	Quest variables
$nade_Var00	Trap active
$nade_Var01	Cell change spell active
$nade_Var02	CrimeSpell active
$nade_Var03	Equipment retrieval quest stage/mode
$nade_Var04	DefeatQuest quest stage
$nade_Var05	GuardPunish quest stage
$nade_Var06	PublicPunish quest stage
$nade_Var07	CaptiveQuest stage
$nade_Var08	CalmQuest stage
$nade_Var09	CloakQuest stage


$nade_IndecencyHL	Guards and Civilians in cities and villages will fuck and punish you if you dont follow the rules. Breaking the rules is: beeing covered in cum, barefoot, naked or dirty, sprinting, running or sneaking. Beeing unarmed also does not help... More options will follow.

$nade_HairRegrowthTimeHL	Game time (hours) needed for the hair to regrow one level (a long hairstyle needs at most three levels to regrow) 

$nade_SlaveryHL	Probability of assaulters enslaving the PC via the Simple Slavery mod (works only with humans and humanoid creatures). You can set SD+ Event chance to send to SD+ local slavery instead (see below - requires the mod SD+ of course)
$nade_CaptivityHL	Probability of getting tied to Bondage Furnitures after Sex. You will be whipped and have to escape via wiggle hotkey.
$nade_ThrowOutHL	Probability of getting thrown out of dungeons and getting tied to outdoor Zaz devices (furnitures) after Sex and getting whipped and electrocuted
$nade_BreakArmorHL	[x] Worn armor pieces can be stripped from hits in combat and the player can be defeated (not killed) by critical hits even with HP left.
$nade_BreakClothingHL	Clothing strip chance per hit
$nade_BreakLightHL	Light armor strip chance per hit
$nade_BreakHeavyHL	Heavy armor strip chance per hit

$nade_HarmlessHL	Enemies don't attack the naked PC - ONLY USE IN COMBINATION WITH CIVILIAN FUCKING MODS
$nade_ProstHL	Player character can offer their body for civilians in exchange for money or devious keys

$nade_BondageHaircut	Haircut chance
$nade_BondageHaircutHL	Probability of shaving the hair before defeat - IMPORTANT: at the moment the hair will not regrow itself. You need to use a wig or racemenu to get your hair back (WIP) 

$nade_EnabledHL	Enable/disable mod

$nade_FinishQuestHL	Give back all stripped equipment and finish running equipment retrieval quest

$nade_WhipMarksHL	Naked Defeat whipping scenes will leave whipmarks on the player character (Required Mods: Rape Tattoos, Fade Tattoos, SlaveTats, Cane Marks textures)
$nade_RapeHandsHL	Naked Defeat Sex scenes will leave handprints on the body (Required Mods: Rape Tattoos, Fade Tattoos, SlaveTats, Rape Hands)
$nade_WhipMarksDuration	Tattoo fadeout time 
$nade_HairCut	Hair shaving before Sex

$nade_Var12HL	Add/remove the PC to/from the zbfFactionSlave faction (faction membership will prevent Civilian Rape)

$nade_DefeatRobberyGold	Rob Gold only
$nade_DefeatRobberyGoldHL	With this on only a random portion of your gold will be stolen, nothing else.

$nade_DefeatSceneProtectors	Enable Scene Protectors 
$nade_DefeatSceneProtectorsHL	[x] improves whipping scenes on the player character by playing an invisible wall object. Can lead to collision problems with the camera, which can be fixed by using free camera.
 
$nade_DefeatDowntime	Delayed Defeat Timer
$nade_DefeatDowntimeHL	This timer starts ticking when you go down in combat (from Bleedout, Stripping hits or similar) but have followers still fighting. At the end of the timer you are either defeated (even when your followers are still alive, they surrender to protect you) or you can get up again (enable "Timer hits 0: Player recovers"). When your followers are all down while the timer runs, you are defeated either way.

$nade_DefeatGetUp	Timer hits 0: Player recovers
$nade_DefeatGetUpHL	If this is enabled and you enter bleedout with your followers still fighting, you will get up again as soon as the Bleedout Timer hits zero and can continue to fight. Your followers protected you.

$nade_DefeatIdleTime	Between Sex Idle Time
$nade_DefeatIdleTimeHL	This adds extra time to the "between Sex idle" scenes that play idly poses. Basically for eye candy/immersion purpose, do with this what you want. Set to 0 to speed transition faster to the next sex scene or aftermath.

$nade_NymSpawning	Nymra's Spawn Service
$nade_NymSpawningHL	With this enabled this will happen: 1. when you enter bleedout but no valid enemies are around, a group of ghosts will spawn to take care of you. 2. when you are defeated and ONLY human actors are around, dogs, horses, tame trolls, goats and similar will spawn to make the scene a bit more "interesting"

$nade_PunishShortProb	Short Punishment Chance
$nade_PunishShortProbHL	Chance that public punishment will only be one scene instead of the full defeat cycle. Can be either one of the following: "Fucking", "Golden Shower", "Bound Whipping", "Wiggle Free", "Pay Fine". This respects your other settings, so whipping or golden showers on 0% will not use those scenes.

$nade_Followers	Follower Management



$nade_AllowArgonKajit	Argonians & Khajiits
$nade_AllowArgonKajitHL	Human Races of Argonians and Khajiits

$nade_AllowHumanoidBeasts	Big Beasts
$nade_AllowHumanoidBeastsHL	Gargoyles, Werewolves, Trolls, Giants, Lurkers

$nade_AllowUndead	Undead
$nade_AllowUndeadHL	Draugr, Skeletons, Dragonpriests, Vampirelords

$nade_AllowRieklings	Rieklings
$nade_AllowRieklingsHL	Rieklings, Boar Riders, Boars

$nade_AllowFalmers	Falmers
$nade_AllowFalmersHL	Falmers

$nade_AllowSpriggans	Spriggans
$nade_AllowSpriggansHL	Spriggans

$nade_AllowElementalsFemale	Misc Creatures (female)
$nade_AllowElementalsFemaleHL	Atronach Flame, WispMothers, Hagravens

$nade_AllowElementalsMale	Misc Creatures (male)
$nade_AllowElementalsMaleHL	Atronach Storm, Atronach Frost, Wisps, IceWraiths

$nade_AllowTentacleStuff	Tentacles
$nade_AllowTentacleStuffHL	Seekers, Netches, Tentacle Animations in Sex Scenes

$nade_AllowInsects	Insects
$nade_AllowInsectsHL	Ashhoppers, Chaurus, Chaurus Hunter, Chaurus Reaper, 

$nade_AllowSpiders	Spiders
$nade_AllowSpidersHL	Spiders, Medium Spiders, Large Spiders

$nade_AllowSabreCats	Sabrecats
$nade_AllowSabreCatsHL	Sabrecats

$nade_AllowSkeevers	Skeevers
$nade_AllowSkeeversHL	Skeevers

$nade_AllowBears	Bears
$nade_AllowBearsHL	Bears

$nade_AllowCanines	Canines
$nade_AllowCaninesHL	Dogs, Wolves

$nade_AllowDragons	Dragons (WIP, not currently supported)
$nade_AllowDragonsHL	not currently supported

$nade_AllowDeers	Deers
$nade_AllowDeersHL	Deers

$nade_AllowFoxes	Foxes
$nade_AllowFoxesHL	Foxes

$nade_AllowRabbits	Rabbits
$nade_AllowRabbitsHL	Rabbits

$nade_AllowHorkers	Horkers
$nade_AllowHorkersHL	Horkers

$nade_AllowMammoths	Mammoths
$nade_AllowMammothsHL	Mammoths

$nade_AllowHorses	Horses
$nade_AllowHorsesHL	Horses

$nade_AllowCows	Cows
$nade_AllowCowsHL	Cows

$nade_NakedLootHotkeys	Use Outfit & Weapon Hotkeys
$nade_NakedLootHotkeysHL	[x] "ALT+(1,2,3,...,0)" will equip (animated) the saved outfit from inventory. Numbers alone (1,2,3,...,0) will equip the saved weapon from inventory. Shift+1: Fists // Shift+2: equip random outift // Shift+3: UnequipAll()

$nade_NakedLoot	Enable Naked Loot
$nade_NakedLootHL	[x] Loot your favourite Outfits and Weapons back from your enemies! Do not enable this if you dont know what you do!!!. Read Documentiation in the Loverslab forum, it is too complex to describe here. 

$nade_DefeatDeathChance	Death/Execution Chance
$nade_DefeatDeathChanceHL	No Death&Reload !!! Contains Guro/Gore/Death and Execution scenes during Naked Defeat or at its end !!! After "Death" you are sent to the Afterlife scenario and wake up in the wild.

$nade_AllowChicken	Chicken
$nade_AllowChickenHL	Chicken

$nade_AllowGoats	Goats
$nade_AllowGoatsHL	Goats

$nade_AllowDwarven	Dwarven Automats
$nade_AllowDwarvenHL	Dwarven Spider, Dwarven Centurion, Dwarven Sphere, Dwarven Ballistas

$nade_LibraryHairs	Hairstyles :Library:
$nade_LibraryOutfitsTags	Outfits :Library:

$nade_OptionsCombat	Combat & Strip :Options:

$nade_OptionsPublicPunish	Public Punishment :Options:

$nade_OptionsExtras	Extra Features :Options:

$nade_OptionsDefeat	Defeat & Sex :Options:

$nade_OptionsAftermath	Aftermath :Options:

$nade_LibrarySlots	Bodyslots :Library:

$nade_LibraryCreatures	Creature Toggles :Library:
